Spots
斑点
Six
六
Fish
鱼
Ah-ah
啊啊
Figaro
费加罗
Wishes
愿望
Spots
斑点
And now the six merry  murderesses of the Captain Hook County Jail
以下是六名快乐谋杀犯
in their rendition of the Spell Block Tango
咒语牢房探戈表演
Spots
斑点
Six
六
Fish
鱼
Ah-ah
啊啊
Figaro
费加罗
Wishes
愿望
Spots
斑点
Six
六
Fish
鱼
Ah-ah
啊啊
Figaro
费加罗
Wishes
愿望
Sports
斑点
Six
六
Fish
鱼
Ah-ah
啊啊
Figaro
费加罗
Wishes
愿望
He had it coming
他自找的
He only had himself to be blame
他自作孽  不可活
If you'd have been there
如果你也在场
if you'd seen it
如果你目睹一切
I bet you you would have done the same
我打赌你也会这么做
Spots
斑点
Six
六
Fish
鱼
Ah-ah
啊啊
Figaro
费加罗
Wishes
愿望
Spots
斑点
Six
六
Fish
鱼
Ah-ah
啊啊
Figaro
费加罗
Wishes
愿望
You know how people have these little habits that get you down
有些人就是有些小习惯来让你失望
like Jasper and Horace
比如像贾斯珀和贺瑞斯
they didn't know their fabrics
他们对衣料一无所知
I asked for spots
我要的是斑点纹
No not stripes
不 不是条纹
not dots
也不是波点
spots
是斑点
So I came on this one day
有天我进了房子
and I'm really irritated
非常生气
And I'm looking for a little bit sympathy
我想要寻求一点点安慰
and there's Jasper and Horace
结果看见了贾斯珀和贺瑞斯
lying on the couch drinking a beer
躺在沙发上喝着啤酒
with ten yards of dotted fabric
旁边还放着十码的波点布料
No not spots
不 不是斑点的
dots
是波点的
So I said to them I said you buy me dots one more time
我告诉他们你们敢再给我买成波点一次
and they did
他们还真的又买了
So l took the shotgun off the wall
于是我拿下挂在墙上的猎枪
and I fired two warning shots
射了两枪警告枪
into their heads
朝他们的脑袋
They had it coming
他们自找的
They only have themselves to blame
他们自作孽 不可活
If you have been there
如果你也在场
if you'd seen it
如果你目赌了一切
I bet you you would have done the same
你打赌你也会这么做
Spots
斑点
Six
六
Fish
鱼
Ah-ah
啊啊
Figaro
费加罗
Wishes
愿望
Spots
斑点
Six
六
Fish
鱼
Ah-ah
啊啊
Figaro
费加罗
Wishes
愿望
I met Doc in a faraway land about two years ago
我两年前在一个遥远的地方遇见了多克
He told me he was single
他说他是单身
and we hit it off right away
我们立马就坠入了爱河
So we started living together
然后开始同居
He'd go to work and little jewel mines and come home singing Heigh Ho
他会去他的宝石矿上工作 回家唱  《嗨吼》
I'd fix him a drink
我会给他倒杯喝的
we'd have dinner
然后一起吃晚餐
and then I found out the single he told me
后来我发现他跟我说的单身
single my glass
单身个玻璃
Not only was he married
他不仅已经结婚了
Oh no he had six men
而且有六个男朋友
One of those dwarfs
小矮人之一
you know
你知道吗
So that night when he came home from work
那晚他下班后回家
I fixed him a drink as usual
我像往常一样给他准备了喝的
You know some guys just can't hold their apple juice
有些人就是等不及要喝手中的苹果汁
He had it coming
他自找的
He took a flower in its prime
他摘了一朵鲜花
And then he used it
然后利用它
And he abused it
摧残它
It was a murder but not a crime
·
·
.
Now I'm standing over the cauldron
我站在大锅旁边
mixing up some catfish for dinner
搅拌着为晚餐准备的鲶鱼
minding my own business
做着我自己的事
In stores Prince Eric in a jealous rage
艾瑞克王子突然冲了进来  带着愤怒的醋意
You've been screwin King Trenton he says
他说 你一直在和川顿国王找麻烦
It was crazy
简直不可理喻
and he kept on screaming you've been screwing King Trenton
他一直大叫着 你一直在找川顿国王的麻烦
and then he ran into my tentacles
然后他就撞在了我的触手上
He ran into my tentacles eight times
他在我的触手上撞了八次
If you'd been there, if you'd seen it
如果你也在场 如果你目睹了一切
I bet you you would have done the same
我打赌你也会这么做
Dumbo, La Duck, Marcus Mouse, Pluto Junior,
小飞象 唐老鸭 米妮 小小布鲁托
Amelia Fieldmouse, Archimedes, Babette, Tiger Lily, Madame de la Grande Bouche,
阿米莉亚 阿基米德 芭贝特 虎莲公主 衣柜管家
Humphrey the Bear, Drusilla, La LeFou, La Mirror, Banzai, Kronk, Slue-Foot Sue .
汉弗来熊  德鲁希拉 来福 魔镜 班仔 高刚 弹跳苏
Yes, but did you do it?
是的 但是你做的吗？
Ah-ah, not guilty
啊啊 我无罪
My brother Mufasa and I had this exact
我哥哥木法沙和我做了这个表演
And my lady Sarabi used to tag along with us
我的妻子沙拉碧总会跟着我们
Never the last number in our act
在我们的上一次表演中
we did these 20 acrobatic tricks in a row
我们连续做了20个杂技表演
One two three four five splits spread eagle back flips
一二三四五 劈叉 雄鹰展翅 后空翻
flip flops one right after the other
一个接一个地空翻
So this one night before the show
在表演前的一个晚上
I go down to the hotel Figaro
我去了费加罗酒店
hanging with the hyenas having a few laps
和土狼们喝了几杯
and they run out of zebra
他们没有斑马了
So I ran out to get some
所以我出门去弄几匹
and I come back into the den
之后我回到巢穴里
and there's Sarabiand Mufasa doing number 17
看见沙拉碧和木法沙在做17式
the spread eagle
雄鹰展翅
Well I was in such a state of shock
我太震惊了
I completely blacked out
大脑一片空白
I don't remember a thing
什么也不记得了
It wasn't untit later when i was washing the blood off my paws
之后我清醒过来 发现我在洗着爪子上的血
Ieven knew they were dead
我甚至还知道他们已经死了
They had it coming
他们自找的
They had it coming all the long
都是他们自作自受
I didn't do it
我没做
He didn't do it
他没做
But if I had done it
但如果我真的做了
But if he had done it
但如果他真的做了
How could you tell me that I was wrong
怎么能说我做错了呢
They had it coming
他们自找的
They had it coming all the long
都是他们自作自受
I didn't do it
我没做
He didn't do it
他没做
But if i had done it
但如果我真的做了
How could you tell me that I was wrong
怎么能说我做错了呢
I loved King Stefan more than you could possibly say
我对斯特凡国王的爱  深到旁人无法想象
He was an artistic guy
他是个充满艺术气息的人
Sensitive and full of wishes
敏感 充满愿望
But he was always trying to find himself
但他总是在寻找自我
He'd go out every night looking for himself and on the way
他每晚都会出去寻找自我
He found Flora Fauna and Merryweather
于是他找到了弗罗拉 芳娜 还有梅里韦瑟
I guess you could say we broke up because of artistic differences
可以说我们分手是因为在艺术上的差异
He saw himself as alive
他将自己视作鲜活
And I saw him dead
我视他为死物
The dirty bam bam bam bam bam bam
说不尽的下流事
They had it coming
他们自找的
They had it coming all the long
一切都是他们自作自受
Cause if they use it
如果他们利用仇恨
I may have use it
我也可以利用仇恨
How could you tell us that we were wrong
怎么能说我们错了呢
He had it coming
他自找的
He only have himself to blame
一切都是他自作孽 不可活
If you'd have been there
如果你也在场
if you'd seen it
如果你目睹一切
I bet you you would have done the same
我打赌你也会这样做
he does one more time
再买一次
single my glass
单身个玻璃
he ran into my tentacles
他撞到了我的触手上
Archemides
阿基米德
number 17
17式
artistic differences
艺术差异
the Spread eagle
雄鹰展翅
Sports
斑点
Six
六
Fish
鱼
Ah-ah
啊啊
Figaro
费加罗
Wishes
愿望